We're going to add one more element to our Egyptian Walk, circling with it.
So as we travel, we're going to think about angling our body.
So we still want to be square on with whoever we're facing, but we're going to angle the lower body, upper body stays square.
So, it's going to be; step, twist, a little bit of twist with the lower body.
But the hip is still going straight up into the rib cage.
Step and twist, again, step, and step, twist, step, lower body.
So what that means is that your feet aren't going to be square on to the wall.
They’re going to be angled slightly.
Okay.
So then as you turn, you're going to angle slightly from the direct line here.
And again here, it will be angled slightly, step and here, step.
Let's try it again, with just plain Ibis arms, you can always vary, vary, put variations on the arms.
Turning the left; step, up, shoulders are square to the wall, step, and step.
Good.